[SIGHING]
(Sheldon:)Morning, old chum.
(Leonard:)-What's going on?
-I've made you breakfast.
(Sheldon:)Juice, coffee...
(Sheldon:)...and pancakes in the shape of some
of your favorite fictional characters.
(Sheldon:)See, here's Frodo.
(Leonard:)-You made Frodo pancakes?
-Yeah, I used coconut shavings...
(Sheldon:)...to do the hair on his feet.
(Sheldon:)If you need to void your bladder
before eating...
(Sheldon:)...I can keep them warm with this beret
that I thoroughly laundered...
(Sheldon:)...and pressed into service
as a pancake cozy.
(Leonard:)Why are you doing this?
(Sheldon:)It's by way of an apology
for my recent behavior.
(Sheldon:)I've had some time to reflect
and I've come to realize...
(Sheldon:)...that friendship is not an aggregation
of written agreements.
It's the result of two people
respecting and caring for each other.